

PERSONAL SKILLS

Reliable
Professional
Organized
Time management
Team player
Fast learner
Motivated
Capability of Analysis
Problem Solving

LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native English: Fluent French: Basic

CONTACT

(438) 372-3351 OrlandoReynoso1983@gmail.com https://orlan2y3.github.io/SysAdmin/ LinkedIn

REFERENCES

Available upon request

ORLANDO REYNOSO

SYSTEM-CLOUD ADMINISTRATOR

HIGHLIGHTS: Successful IT support and system administrator with more than 16 years of experience in the field. always stimulating myself and my coworkers to work hard looking to achieve beyond the expected results refreshing knowledge and creativity. My collaborative leadership, persuasive skills, positive attitude, and solid work ethic have allowed me to obtain a solid knowledge of many technologies and teamwork. I can prioritize, work under pressure, and meet deadlines. I am always highly motivated to learn new things from everyone around me. Seeking to use my expertise, skills, and abilities to contribute to your organization's success.

TECHNOLOGIES AND TOOLS I HAVE HANDLED

- Certified Cloud Azure Administrator
- Microsoft Office365 Administrator
- Microsoft on-premises Administrator (AD, GPO, Etc.)
- Email Server Exchange 2016 and MDaemon
- Firewall (SonicWALL and FortiGate)
- Virtualization Citrix, XenApp and Hyper-V
- Networking LAN
- Networking WiFi (Cisco Meraki and Ruckus)
- Monitoring Tools (LANSweeper, Event Sentry, Goliath, PDQ)
- Backup (Backup Exec and Veeam)
- Storage (TrueNAS and Synology)
- Antivirus (Trend Micro Apex One)
- · Scripting with PowerShell
- Google Domain for Chromebooks
- KnowBe4 Security Awareness Training
- Ticketing Sytems (Jira, Service Desk, and Confluence)
- OS (Windows, MacOS, Linux, iOS, and Andriod)
- Hardware (PC and Printers)
- IP Telephony with Avaya IP Office
- Programming (HTML, CSS, JS, GIT, VB.Net)
- Microsoft SOL
- Web Server IIS
- Surveillance and Access Control Systems

EDUCATION

BACHELOR IN BUSINESS INFORMATICS | SUMMA CUM LAUDE

UNIVERSIDAD ABIERTA PARA ADULTOS (UAPA), SANTIAGO, D.R. 2011 - 2015

EXPERIENCE

SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR

HARDT | 2022 - CURRENT

Maintains, configures, and troubleshoots networks and computer systems. Monitoring and installing software and hardware, improving the performance of systems, and providing technical support to users.

APPLICATION SUPPORT ENGINEER

VISIUMKMS | 2020 - 2022

Managing ticket workload, escalating issues where appropriate, and providing resolution to issues. Liaising with internal Customer Managers, Service Desk, Incident and Problem Managers, and Change Managers, whilst being involved in the management of major incidents and performance reporting. Troubleshooting issues in the product (application and data), Creating Microsoft SQL Server scripts to identify and correct data integrity issues in customers' data.

IT SUPPORT MANAGER AND SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR

MEPyD | 2013 - 2020

Maintains, configures, and troubleshoots networks and computer systems. Monitoring and installing software and hardware, improving the performance of systems, and providing technical support to users.

Manager of 7 technicians in the technology department to provide quality service.

IT SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR

CENTRO MEDICO SANTIAGO APOSTOL | 2009 - 2013

Managed, configured, and troubleshoot computers, networks, information systems, and databases, and ensured related issues to information technology worked effectively. Provided our users with the best experience possible using our computer and systems.

SYSTEM SUPPORT TECHNICIAN

ARS-CMD | 2004 - 2007 --- COMPUNET | 2007 - 2009

Configured and troubleshot employee attendance systems and card printers. Managed the local network company and its information systems.

Provided professional assistance configuring and troubleshooting our local network, information systems, servers, printer, and computers.